字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
你这次真是搞砸了  巴里
You really did it this time, Barry.
-真的吗  -是的
- Seriously? - Yeah, yeah.
我说真的
Yeah, seriously!
-你到星城寻求我的帮助  -好吧
- You come to Star City, you ask for my help, - OK.
之后不出所料
and then, inevitably,
我们马上就处于困境了
immediately, we end up up the creek!
好吧  这挺公平的  真是谢谢你
Yeah, okay. That's fair. Thank you.
他们来了
They're moving in.
数到三  队长
On three, Team Leader.
这是什么
What's that?
那是热视线
That would be heat vision.
-三  -行动
- Three. - Okay.
闪电侠
第三季
第八集
四   剧
联动集
Part2
10小时之前
他测试的结果一次比一次快
Kid gets faster every time we test him.
-两倍音速  -已经这么快了吗
- Mach 2. - Already?
他几天前才获得的神速力
He just got his speed a few days ago.
他的生命体征如何
How are his vitals?
他的跑步效率  乳酸门槛
His running economy, lactate threshold
远远高于预期水平
are all way above expected levels.
我们手上出奇才了喔
I think we might have a little prodigy on our hands.
就像巫师奇才那种
Like a Wizard of Whiz.
大伙们  我不想让沃利觉得自己是巴里
Guys, I don't want Wally thinking that he's Barry,
鲁莽行事
rushing off half-cocked,
在下一次炼金术师或者萨维塔现身时
trying to take down Alchemy or Savitar
就尝试打倒他们
the next time one of them shows up.
好吧  但大伙们  沃利不像我
Okay, but guys, Wally's not like me.
他不想失去自己的超能力
He doesn't want his powers gone.
我们要说服他不用超能力会很困难
We're gonna have a hard time convincing him not to use them.
是啊  但他准备好之前我们必须得说服他
Yeah, well, we have to. Until he's ready.
怎么说服
How?
告诉他他并没有准备好
By convincing him that he isn't.
这意味着不要鼓励他  不要训练他
That means no encouraging him, no training him,
还有你...
and you...
不要和他说战衣的事  拜托了
no talking to him about a suit, please.
为了他好
It's for his own good.
为什么不说
Why the hell not?
又是一个朋友之间的谎言  是吧
It's just another lie between friends, right?
西斯科
Cisco.
怎么了
What?
还是不好吗
Still not good?
我觉得或许明天再试试吧
I think maybe we should try again tomorrow.
我可以再多进行一些测试
I can run a few more tests.
已经很棒了
That was amazing.
晚饭我请  想吃什么都行
Dinner's on me. Whatever you want.
测试测试  尖端科研实验室的成员们
Test. Test. Fellow S.T.A.R. Labs employees.
麻烦你们来表层控制室
Your presence in the cortex would be greatly appreciated.
今晚他要演讲吗
That's tonight? His presentation?
太棒了
Great.
你觉得  这事过后  我们喝一杯如何
What do you think if, after, maybe we get a drink?
你  我还有巴里
You, me, Barry?
巴里  我们就只是喝一杯
Barry? We're just gonna get drinks?
假装还是好朋友吗
Pretend like we're friends?
想得美
Nice try.
不可能的
It ain't gonna happen.
尖端科研实验室
爆裂观光活动
你想让尖端科研实验室对大众公开吗
You want to open S.T.A.R. Labs to the public?
两个星期后吗
In two weeks?
小型的开张典礼  不会大肆铺张
Soft open. Not a hard open.
但是我会用你提供的建议
But, you know, I'll use your input.
现在非常重要
All right? Right now, it's very important
因为时间紧迫
'cause the clock is ticking.
我的预想包括  但不限于
My vision is set to include, but not limited to--
亲自带大家参加这栋实验室
bam-- a personal transportation tour of the facility.
尖端科研实验室博物馆
或者对胆小的人来说  我们还有
Or, for the faint of heart, we have--
虚拟现实可供选择
pow-- a virtual reality alternative.
两个项目都包括了粒子幻象
Both set to include particle vision.
粒子...  幻象
Particle... vision?
粒子幻象  就是粒子加速器爆炸的
Particle vision, which is a moment-to-moment reenactment
场景即时再现
of the particle accelerator explosion,
但是从这一角度来看...
but seen from the point of view of...
-粒  -粒子
- Part-- - The particle!
HR  我知道你想尽办法
Listen, H.R., I know that you're trying to figure out
让自己为团队提供价值  我明白  但是
how you add value to the team, I get it, but this--
不好意思打断你  BA
Let me stop you right there, B.A.
-别叫我BA  -我能让尖端科研实验室
- Okay, don't call me B.A.-- - I can make S.T.A.R. Labs
像以前一样成为科学界的权威
the powerhouse in the scientific community that it once was,
并且
and, moreover,
赢回人们的信任
earn back the people's trust.
看看你们
Look at you guys.
你们一副愁眉不展的样子
You just-- your faces are so darn gloomy.
我们要这样做  我要让你们...
Here's what we'll do. I'm gonna make you guys a--
是人造卫星吗
Was that-- was that the satellite?
希望不是人造卫星
I hope that wasn't the satellite.
是流星吗
Is that a meteor?
是的  是流星
Why, yes, that is a meteor,
没错  正朝市中心袭来
and yes, it is heading for downtown.
我得走了
I got to go.
各位
Guys.
是什么
What is it?
巴里  你看到了什么
Barry, what do you see?
这不是流星
This isn't a meteor.
巴里  巴里  回话
Barry? Hey, Barry, come in.
-听到我说话吗  -各位
- Can you hear me? - Guys?
不是吧
Oh, come on.
外星人
Aliens!
政府官员正在上报
Government officials are reporting
在中城市中心坠毁的神秘物体
the mysterious object that crashed in downtown Central City
只是美国国防部一架例行演习的飞机
was simply a DOD aircraft on a routine training operation.
谢谢  但我们会向白宫汇报的
Thank you, but we'll brief the White House.
你没注意听我说
You're not listening to me about this.
我们在超能力联合调查组搜集到的情报
The intelligence we've gathered at A.R.G.U.S.--
并不准确
Is not accurate.
我们已经掩盖了这件事  麦考斯指挥官
We've got this covered, Director Michaels.
回星城吧
Go back to Star City.
让上级接手
Let the big guns take over.
莱拉  怎么回事
Lyla, what is this?
我看到坠毁的那艘奇怪飞船
I saw the weird ship that crashed--
你看到了飞船  还看到什么吗
You saw a ship? What else did you see?
足以让雷利·史考特做噩梦了
Enough to give Ridley Scott nightmares.
英国导演
去尖端科研实验室汇合
Meet me at S.T.A.R. Labs.
到时告诉你我知道的一切
I'll tell you everything I know.
外星人吗
Aliens?
它们是《异形》那种外星人还是小绿人
Are they "Alien" Aliens or little green men?
都有一点
Both, sort of.
自从我们知道它们后
Since we learned of them,
我们一直称它们为支配者
we've been calling them the Dominators.
这个名字可不是
That is not the name
什么为和平而来的种族叫的
of a species that comes in peace.
对  对  这可是很有侵略性的名字
No, no, it's very aggressive.
所以你们知道支配者有多久了
So how long have you known about these Dominators?
自从五十年代以来
Since the '50s.
那时就是它们吗  雷德蒙德  俄勒冈州
That was them. Redmond, Oregon.
政府试图进行隐瞒
The government tried to cover it up.
怎么  我看科幻频道啊
What? I watch Syfy channel.
在1951年  它们在相同的情况下出现了
In 1951, they appeared under the same sort of circumstances.
飞船坠毁  基本上没有交流
A ship crash-landed. Little to no communication.
我们了解到它们在绑架人类
We learned they were abducting humans
来收集关于我们的资料
to gather intel about us.
它们发起进攻  数百名士兵牺牲了生命
They attacked, and hundreds of soldiers lost their lives.
然后因为某种未知的原因  它们离开了
Then, for some inexplicable reason, they left.
所有联系都消失了  直到三个月前
All contact had been lost until three months ago
美国国防部接收到了这个
when the DOD received this.
我们没有威胁  人类居民
We pose no threat, human inhabitants.
理解是我们的目的
Understanding is our purpose.
任何如过往一般  针对我们的行动
Any action against us, as shown to us in the past,
将会受到即刻反击
will prompt swift retaliation.
所以当我们发现四艘飞船向地球而来时
So when we discovered four ships heading towards Earth,
我们担心历史将会重演
we were concerned that it was happening all over again.
显然  其中一个  降落到了这里
One of them, obviously, landed here.
好吧  就好像我们中城这里的怪事
Right, 'cause we ain't got enough crazy going on here
还不够多似的
in Central City.
你知道它们想要什么吗
Do you know what they want?
它们无视了所有沟通的企图
They've ignored all attempts to communicate,
但是我们知道  就像之前一样
but we do know, just like before,
那降落艇装载着侦查小队
that the dropships contain reconnaissance teams
派来这里收集关于我们的资料
sent here to gather more intel about us.
寻找我们的弱点
Looking for our weaknesses.
-我们得做些什么  -我们在做
- We need to do something. - We are.
基本上联合国中的所有国家
Nearly every member state in the UN is in talks
都在进行合作谈判
to coordinate a response.
已经有行动开始了
Action is being taken.
等等  你是想让我们别插手这事吗
So, wait, you want us to just sit this one out?
那些家伙就像是《末日之战》里的僵尸
These things are like "World War Z" Zombies.
如果它们决定进攻  没有军队能阻止它们
If they decide to attack, no military can stop them.
你也不能
Neither could you.
至少靠你自己不行
Not by yourself, anyway.
现在就先让我们来处理这事吧
Just let us handle this. For now.
咱们保持联络
I will be in touch.
所以我们的计划不是就这样
So the plan isn't to just stay still
坐以待毙  对吧
and do nothing, right?
不是
No.
巴里  你听到莱拉说的了
Barry, you heard Lyla.
你不能一个人单干
You can't do this alone.
我也不打算单干
I don't plan to.
星城
找到什么了吗
Anything?
没有
Zilch.
他肯定在这里某个地方
He's got to be here somewhere.
有没有可能这个人突然觉得
What are the chances the guy just decided
他受够了他现在的生活呢
that he had enough of this life, you know?
又没有医保
No health insurance.
受够了这种疯狂生活
He was sick of the crazy hours.
子弹也都不便宜  而且他...
I mean, bullets aren't actually that cheap, and he--
-抱歉了  哥们  -没事
- I'm sorry, man. I-- - It's okay.
天啊
Man...
你好  巴里
Hi,  Barry.
那个人是谁
So, who was that guy?
治安维持者  我们差点就抓到他了
That was Vigilante, and we nearly had him.
你差点就抓到他了吗  奥利
You nearly had him, Ollie?
看起来他可是要
It looked like he was about to
像《疤面煞星》里那样干掉你们了
"Scarface" you guys.
巴里  有什么我能帮你的吗
Barry, is there something that I can do for you?
又要帮你打败一个邪恶的极速者还是
Another evil speedster to help you with or--
有可能真需要  不过我来不是因为那事
Maybe, actually. That's not why I'm here, though.
什么事这么着急让你跑来星城
What's so urgent that you had to rush to Star City?
有外星人
Aliens.
外星人
Aliens?
Aliens.
巴里  我向上帝保证
I swear to God, Barry.
在我遇见你之前  我的生活还算正常
My life was somewhat normal before I met you.
我很抱歉
I-- I mean, I'm sorry.
听着  真的有外星人  而且它们已经来了
Look, okay, they're real, and they're already here,
根据莱拉所说的来看
and, from what Lyla told us,
它们可不是来友好相处的
it does not appear to be for peace.
-糟了  -莱拉知道这事吗
- Oh, no. - Lyla knows about this?
莱拉  对的  她来找我们...
Lyla-- yeah, she came to--
你要去哪
where are you--
我叫来了西娅
I called Thea.
我来让你签了这个
Yeah, I came to have you sign this
趁着市政局还没有暴乱
before City Council went in to mutiny,
但这个绝对可以等等再说
but that can totally wait.
算我一个
Count me in.
算你什么  你不是退役了吗
For what? I thought you retired.
是啊  但这可是外星人啊
Yeah, but it's-- it's aliens.
真是太有爱了
Aw, that is so cute.
你们要集结起来
You guys are just gonna get together
去大战外星人  你们都疯了吗
and go fight some aliens-- have you lost your mind?
它们是外星人  而且你们只有四个人
They're aliens, and there's only four of you.
我们还可以叫来斯泰因  和其他那些人
Not if we get Stein and, you know, all the others.
他们管自己叫传奇
They're calling themselves the Legends.
好自负  不过很顺口
Egotistical but catchy.
你知道他们在哪吗
Do you know where they are?
我知道他们曾经在哪
I know where they were.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
这是尖端科研实验室的一个老飞机仓库
It's this old hall hangar thing that S.T.A.R. Labs owns.
或者说是我的
Or I guess I own it.
那你该好好利用起来的
Well, you should do something with it.
好了  我来理一理
All right, so let me get this right.
我们那些坐着时间飞船的小伙伴们
Our time-traveling buddies in a flying timeship
会在这里冒出来  对吗
are supposed to just pop up right here, right?
对  我给了他们这个时间和地点
Yeah. This is the time and place I gave them,
所以如果他们收到了我的消息
so if they got my message,
他们现在就应该...
they should be here--
来了
Right now.
你知道我为什么从来都不嗑药吗
You know why I've never done drugs?
因为我怕看见诡异的东西
It's 'cause I was always afraid I'd see weird stuff.
带大家进去  好吗
Okay, take everybody inside, all right?
-告诉奥利弗我马上回来  -你要去哪里
- Tell Oliver I'll be right back. - Where are you going?
既然我们要大战外星人
Well, since we're fighting aliens,
我想不如也给咱们自己找来一个
I figured we should get one of our own, right?
你找到对应的地球了吗
You found the right Earth?
超光子机检测到你跟她见面是在地球38
Tachyon device tracked you on Earth-38 when you met her,
-所以应该在那里能找到她  -好的
- so you should find her there. - All right.
你要知道  我这么做
Just so you know, I'm only doing this
只是为了完成任务
because we're on a mission.
我不会让个人恩怨妨碍任务进行
I'm not gonna let my issues with you get in the way of that.
可能得试好几次
This might take a few tries.
纳欣诺市
这里最好是正确的地方
This better be the right place.
因为如果地方不对
'Cause if this isn't the right place,
有人就要一头雾水了
someone's about to be real confused.
巴里
Barry?
我就知道
I knew it!
我就知道是你
I knew that was you.
我就知道是你在那个奇怪的时空...
I knew it was you in that weird space--
对不起  试了好几次才传到这儿
Sorry, it took a couple tries to get here.
这是我的朋友  西斯科
This is my friend, Cisco.
"朋友"形容得不太准确  我们是同事
Well, friend is a loose term. We work together.
你好  西斯科
Hi. Cisco.
我得说
I have to say it--
你这个宇宙挺棒的
this is a nice universe you got here.
谢谢
Thank you.
你还记得去年
Okay, do you remember last year
我帮你的时候
when I helped you out
你答应过将来会为我做同样的事吗
and you promised to do the same for me?
我们的敌人是谁
What are we up against?
这边是绿箭队
Team Arrow is here.
这边是传奇队
Team Legends is here.
-这就都到齐了吧  -是的吧
- Is that everyone? - I think so?
内特和阿玛雅留守乘波号
Nate and Amaya are back watching the Waverider.
俩新来的
The newbies.
太酷炫了
That was cool.
各位
Guys
感谢大家过来
Thanks for coming.
巴里  你不是要带外星人过来吗
Barry, I thought you were bringing an alien.
对  带来了
And, yeah, we did.
各位  这是我朋友卡拉·丹弗斯
Everybody, this is my friend, Kara Danvers,
在她的地球上也叫超女
or, as she's known on her Earth, Supergirl.
她哪里"超"了
What makes her so super?
这个嘛
Well?
我信了
I'm convinced.
史上最佳团队
Best. Team-up. Ever!
装备准备好了
您有什么指示
把人类领袖带过来
战争还未打响就会终结
尖端
科研
实验室
好了  我想我都记住了
Okay. I think I have this.
-奥利弗  -绿箭侠
- Oliver. - Green Arrow.
-狄格  -斯巴达
- Dig. - Spartan.
-西娅  -快手
- Thea. - Speedy.
好
Okay.
-莎拉  -白金丝雀
- And Sara. - White Canary.
-杰克斯和斯泰因教授  -火风暴
- Jax and Professor Stein. - Firestorm.
-雷  -帕尔默  原子侠
- Ray. - Palmer. The Atom.
还有米克
And Mick.
热浪
Heat Wave.
然后是...
And...
爱瑞丝  凯特琳和费利西蒂
Iris, Caitlin, and Felicity.
好棒
Yes!
而你有冰冻能力  但是却不能使用
And you, you have cold powers, but you can't use them?
-你有超能力  -说来话长了
- You have powers? - It's a long story.
巴里  奥利弗·奎恩就是绿箭侠吗
Barry, so, Oliver Queen is the Green Arrow?
-是的  -天呐
- Yeah. - Oh, my God.
-那现在他更性感了  -天呐
- He just got so much hotter. - Oh my God.
西斯科  我们该开始干正事了吧
Okay, Cisco, we should probably get started.
这就是支配者
These are the Dominators.
关于它们的信息我们掌握得很少
We don't know much about them.
除了它们非常强大
Except they're really strong.
小时候我听说过很多它们的故事
I-I heard a lot of stories about them when I was a kid.
我还没出生的时候它们就来到了我的星球
They came to my planet before I was born.
它们在很多人身上做了实验
They did experiments on a lot of people.
杀害的人更多
Killed a lot more.
不过不只是它们
Well, they're not the only ones
拥有超人的力量吧
with superhuman strength, I hear.
巴里说你比火车头的力量还大
Barry says that you're more powerful than a locomotive.
我们可以把卡拉当做训练的假想敌
We should use Kara as a stand-in for training.
什么时候轮到这个罗宾汉发号施令了
Since when is Robin Hood calling the shots?
米克的意思是
What I think Mick is trying to say
我们应该确定一下谁来当总指挥
is it would be nice if we knew who was in charge around here.
我们投票好了
Maybe we should take a vote.
选个队长出来  选一个我们都信任的人
Choose a leader. Someone we can all trust.
我相信奥利弗  我投他一票
Well, I trust Oliver. He's got my vote.
非常感激  西斯科
Appreciate that, Cisco,
但巴里把我们召集到了一起
but Barry put us all together.
队长应当是他
It should be him.
也有道理
Fair enough.
好吧
Okay.
行  好吧  那么我想  作为队长
Cool, all right, well, I guess as Team Leader,
首先我们该做的就是开始...
first thing to do is start out by...
-模拟一次进攻  -我们来模拟一次进攻
- Doing a test run. - Let's do a test run.
对  我们来模拟一次进攻
Yeah, let's do a test run.
-以超女为假想敌  -以超女为假想敌
- Against Supergirl. - Against Supergirl, all right?
以超女为假想敌模拟一次进攻
Test run against Supergirl.
我们是不是要假装
Are we just supposed to pretend
没有听见他在说话呀
like we don't hear him?
所以大家就换上装备吧  拿出点干劲
So just suit up. Mm-kay? Look alive.
我们以外星人为训练对象来训练对战外星人
We're training to fight aliens by fighting an alien, so...
-快去吧  -大家换上装备
- Do it. - Suit up.
-别说了  -怎么了
- Stop. - What?
奥利弗  卡拉  和你们说几句
Oliver. Hey. Kara. Really quick.
我很激动你们两个现在见面了
I was excited about the two of you guys meeting each other.
奥利弗是第一个训练我的人
Oliver was the first person to train me.
-真的  -是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
你把他训练得很好呀
Well, you did a really good job.
因为我没有手下留情
It's 'cause I didn't hold back.
我射中了他一箭  你也不能手下留情
I shot him. You can't hold back either.
-他确实射中了我一箭  -好狠
- He did shoot me. - Ouch.
好吧  你确定吗
Okay. Are you sure about that?
我可才刚刚认识这些人
I just met these people--
这些人需要知道
These people need to understand
这会是一场艰难的战斗
this isn't gonna be easy.
不要手下留情  尤其是对我
Don't hold back. Especially against me.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
他是不喜欢我吗
Does he not like me?
他对每个人都这样  时间久了就好了
He's like that with everyone. He'll warm up to you.
老西部的矮星加上复制器  就有了这新战衣
Old West Dwarf Star plus Replicator, equals new suit.
我想说  雷
You know what, Ray?
可能就我这么想  这战衣需要更新了
Maybe it's just me, but I think this thing's due for an update.
是的
Yes.
但要在我们支配了支配者之后了
But after we dominate the Dominators.
我知道你之前在那是干嘛的了
I see what you did there.
我得去干活了
Listen. I got to get to work.
费利西蒂在等我
Felicity's waiting for me.
我们之后再聊
But we'll talk about this later.
巴里
Hey, Barry.
史纳特在哪
Where's Snart?
我很抱歉  巴里  我忘了我们没告诉过你
Man, I'm sorry, Barry. I forgot that we never told you.
发生了什么
What happened?
他牺牲了自己  救了大家
He sacrificed himself. Saved us all.
-他是个英雄  -是个传奇
- He died a hero. - A Legend.
沃利  你来这儿干什么
Wally, what are you doing here?
你不能就这么出现
You can't just show up and think
想着要和其他人一起训练
you're gonna train with everyone else.
为什么不呢
Why not?
因为我们要给你做更多的测试
Because we need to test you more.
HR说我的测试结果很棒
HR Said that my results were great.
他说我可以来
He said I'm good to go.
我不管HR怎么说  你还没准备好
I don't care what HR Said. You are not ready.
-我准备好了  -沃利
- I am ready. - Wally.
这里的所有人都干这行很久了
Everyone here has been doing this
而这次还是他们面对过的
for a long time, and this is gonna be
最艰难的挑战
the hardest challenge they have faced.
对抗炼金术师  萨维塔  或者外星人
Fighting Alchemy or Savitar or aliens
不是你可以轻易尝试的
isn't something you just show up and try.
如果你搞砸了  你会死的
If you screw up, you could die.
你懂吗
Do you-- do you get that?
好吧
Great.
卫星没有发现什么异常
Satellite's not picking up anything abnormal.
没有
No.
我不知道能不能通过这种方式找到支配者
I don't know if we're gonna find any Dominators this way.
我不禁注意到
I--just, I couldn't help but notice
气氛有点紧张
things are a little bit tense.
不用震波也能知道
You don't need to be able to Vibe to figure that out.
好吧  显然  生巴里的气
Okay, so apparently, it's, like, illegal
就是违法的
to be mad at Barry, but guess what.
但是他搞砸了  和其他人一样
He screws up, just like the rest of us.
他搞砸了的时候
Yeah, and when he does, he feels bad
也和其他人一样难过
like the rest of us too.
费利西蒂  他擅自
Felicity, he took it upon himself
改变了时间线
to change the timeline.
因为这样  我的哥哥死了
And because of it, my brother was killed.
所以他怎样难过
So there's no amount of feeling bad
都无济于事
that could ever make up for that.
巴里
Barry.
我们开始训练之前
Before we start training,
你得听听这个
there's something you need to hear.
一则消息  最好可以
A message that would be better
单独给你听
if we could share with you in private.
-好的  我回避  -不用  没关系
- All right, I'll step away. - No, no, it's fine.
你可以留下
You can stay.
可以  但不能有别人了
All right, but no one else.
好的
All right.
我们快点
Let's make it quick.
战争即将到来  亨特船长
A war is coming, Captain Hunter,
在某个时刻  你会被召回
and at some point you're gonna be called back
到中城去为之战斗
to Central City to fight it.
你要知道  你和你的团队
So you need to know that, while you and your team
处在时光穿梭区时
have been in the Temporal Zone,
我做了一个影响时间线的选择
I made a choice that affected the timeline.
如你所知  无论你何时篡改过去
As you know, whenever you alter the past,
都会对现在产生影响
those changes affect the present
并影响未来
and get compounded in the future.
你回来时  将处于我创造的新时间线中
When you return, you will be in the new timeline I created,
届时你们所有人的过去和将来
where everyone's past and everyone's future
都已被影响  包括你自己
has been affected, including yours.
你回来时  不要相信任何事或任何人
When you come back, don't trust anything or anyone.
连我也别信
Not even me.
你从哪弄到这个的
Where did you get that from?
我们是在乘波号上的一间密室中找到的
We found it in a secret room inside the Waverider.
是40年后的你发来的
It was sent by you, 40 years from now.
40年后的巴里
40 years from now?
巴里  这到底是什么意思
Barry, what the hell does this mean?
这是在说我在改变过去时把事情搞砸了
It means I screwed things up when I changed the past.
你干了什么
What did you do?
我回到了过去
I went back in time,
救了我妈妈
and I saved my mom.
我创造了一条她没有死的时间线
I created a timeline where she's alive.
叫做闪点
It's called Flashpoint.
我在那条时间线中生活了几个月
I lived in it for a few months,
我才发现我铸成大错
until I realized that I made a big mistake,
然后我试着重置时间线
and I tried to reset the timeline,
想让一切回归原位
put things back to how they were supposed to be,
可是...
but--
可是于事无补
But it didn't work.
是的
No.
巴里  这简直...
Barry, that's...
那你这么做之后  有什么改变了
So what's changed since you did this?
西斯科的哥哥死了  凯特琳拥有了超能力
Cisco's brother is dead. Caitlin has powers.
狄格尔本来有个女儿  现在变成儿子了
Diggle has a son now instead of a daughter.
什么  约翰有个女儿
What? John had a daughter?
我搞砸的不仅仅是自己的生活  兄弟
I didn't just screw up my life, man.
我搞砸了所有人的生活
I screwed up everybody's lives
而且很明显  包括所有人的未来
and, apparently, everybody's lives in the future.
现在我感觉  这些外星人到这里时
It felt like, when these aliens got here,
终于有件事不是因我而起的
that finally something had happened I didn't cause,
也许我能弥补
and maybe I could make up
我对大家造成的一切  可是我...
for everything I'd done to everybody, but I--
我觉得我们应该坦白告诉大家
I think we should be on the up and up with everybody.
我们得告诉他们
We got to tell 'em.
我们现在要对付一帮外星人
We're going up against a bunch of aliens,
你却想告诉人们
and you want to tell people
他们的生活也许被时间旅行影响了
that their lives might have been affected by time travel?
科幻问题还是一个一个解决吧
One sci-fi problem at a time.
你犯了个错误  巴里
You made a mistake, Barry.
这在所难免
It's part of the job.
但今天我们没法处理这个
But we can't deal with it today.
斯泰因教授  你没事吧
Professor Stein, are you okay?
我不是很确定
I'm not sure.
斯诺女士  你介不介意陪我回趟家
Ms. Snow, would you mind accompanying me to my home?
有件事我必须得去做
There's something I need to do.
当然
Sure.
她真的是挺厉害的
She really is a badass.
是啊  这还真有点性感
Yeah, it's kind of hot.
我们再来一次
Let's go again.
所以这就是
So this is, what,
你建议我不采取任何行动的方式吗
your way of advising me to do nothing?
支配者目前尚未采取
The Dominators have yet to engage
任何侵略行动  长官
in an act of aggression, sir.
超能力联合调查组怎么看
What does A.R.G.U.S. think?
我认为我们无动于衷就正中它们下怀了
I think us being passive is exactly what they want,
总统先生
Mr. President.
终于  有勇敢的人站出来说话了
Well, finally, someone here with balls.
艾克忽视了所有征兆  最后为时已晚
Ike ignored all the signs and waited until it was too late.
艾克即艾森豪威尔  美国第34任总统
我不会犯同样的错误
I'm not gonna make that same mistake.
你也看到上一次
You saw what happened
我们与它们交火的结果了
the last time we engaged them.
由此带来的大量伤亡  我们应该谨记
That's a lot of casualties to be remembered for.
四艘降落艇登陆地球
Four dropships landed on this planet,
都是来收集情报的
all of them sent to gather intel.
如果我们不行动而它们发起了进攻
If we do nothing and they attack,
我就会因为这个而被铭记了
that's what I'll be remembered for.
按指示继续行动
Proceed as instructed.
你知道吗  麦考斯指挥官
You know, Director Michaels,
阿曼达·沃勒能领导超能力联合调查组那么久
the reason that Amanda Waller lasted as long as she did
就是因为她懂得如何服从我的领导
is because she learned how to follow my lead.
我建议你学一学她这个优点
I suggest that you acquire that trait.
尽快
Soon.
他不见了
He's gone.
旅行者被劫走了
Traveller has been taken.
重复  旅行者被劫走了
I repeat, Traveller has been taken.
支配者劫走了总统
The Dominators have the President.
-好啊  儿子  -我不明白  爸爸
- Hey, son. - I don't understand, Dad.
这个家里没人希望我拥有超能力
No one in this family wants me to have powers.
你不希望  巴里不希望
You don't. Barry doesn't.
连爱瑞丝也是
Even Iris.
根据这上面的结果显示  我一切正常
According to this, everything's fine with me.
实际上  一切远比正常要好
In fact, everything is better than fine.
怎么  你急着赶回来
What, did you run back
是想确保我不看到这些结果吗
to make sure I didn't see these?
我现在跑得比你快了  还记得吗
I'm faster than you now, remember?
不论你  巴里或是任何人喜欢与否
Whether you or Barry or anyone likes it or not.
沃利  听着
Wally, look.
我知道你对我很生气
I know you're upset with me.
我只是在试图保护你
I was just trying to protect you.
得了吧  我知道你不想让我接受训练
Come on. I know you don't want me training.
我只是不明白为什么
I just don't get why.
因为我比巴里刚刚获得超能力时表现得更好
Because I'm better than Barry was when he first got his speed.
你知道吗  在闪点
You know, in Flashpoint,
我们俩是姐弟打击罪犯小分队
you and I were a brother-sister crime-fighting unit.
所以你不像在那边一样对我那么有信心
So it sucks you don't have the same faith in me here
这真是糟透了
as you did there.
姐弟打击罪犯小分队
Brother and sister crime-fighting unit?
你好  华莱士
Hi, there, Wallace.
我回来拿点润唇膏
I came back to get some lip balm.
没关系  你似乎是这里唯一一个
It's okay. You seem to be the only one
会和我说实话的人了
that'll tell me the truth around here.
我吗
Me?
我们差不多待遇一样  对吗
We're kind of treated the same way, right?
没人尊重我们
No one shows us any respect.
尊重  我只是在试着赢得尊重  华莱士
Respect, I'm just trying to earn that, Wallace.
也许我们应该停止听他们的指挥了
Maybe we should stop listening to them.
是啊  什么  你这话什么意思
Yeah, what? What does that mean?
意思是我想让你训练我
It means I want you to train me.
-我吗  -是的
- Me? - Mm-hmm.
电影演员  一般饰演硬汉角色
那我的动作会比连姆·尼森电影的笑点切换还快
I would be gone faster than humor in a Liam Neeson movie.
懂我的意思吗
Do you know what I mean?
-不懂  -是的
- No. - Yeah.
-不让他们发现就行  -华莱士
- Not if they don't find out. - Wallace.
拜托  没有人愿意帮我的
Come on. No one's gonna do this for me.
我想有所成就  HR
I want to make a difference, H.R.
不会运用超能力的话
I'm never gonna be able to
我就永远做不到了
if I don't know how to use my powers.
拜托了  我和你一样愿意帮助别人
Please. I want to help people, same as you do.
所以教教我
So show me how.
算了
Nah.
谢谢你陪我来  亲爱的
Thank you for joining me, my dear.
不客气  反正我在那边也没什么用
Of course. I wasn't being much help back there anyway.
要知道  拥有超能力并不是无药可救
You know, having powers isn't exactly a death sentence,
无论你的二重身是什么人
no matter who your doppelganger is.
我袭击了朋友们  最好的朋友们
I attacked my friends-- my best friends--
还说了非常非常可怕的话
and said horrible, horrible things to them.
但那不是你
But that wasn't you.
相信我  作为一个有时要和别人
And believe me, as a person who sometimes shares a body
共用身体的人  我知道其中的区别
with another human being, I know the difference,
你朋友也知道
and so do your friends.
我就是很害怕
I'm just so scared.
万一她回来  我却阻止不了呢
What if she comes back and I can't keep her out?
那时怎么办
Then what?
我们会一起帮你
We'll all be there for you.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你回来了
You're back!
抱歉  我想找我的妻子
I'm sorry. I was looking for my wife.
真好笑  她不在这
Very funny. She's not here.
见到你可真好  我太想念你了
Oh, it's so good to see you. I missed you so much.
是吗
Did you?
当然了  我爱你  爸爸
Of course. I love you, Dad.
我也爱你
I love you too.
但抱歉  我们得走了
But I'm sorry. We have to go.
请你...
Please--
告诉你妈妈  我们很快会见面
tell your mother I'll see her soon.
-斯泰因教授  -我们必须得走了
- Professor Stein? - We have to leave now.
你在哪呢
Where are you?
战争即将到来  亨特船长
A war is coming, Captain Hunter--
你们确定还想我继续吗
Are you sure you want me to keep going?
是的  确定
Yeah. Yes.
但先给我们五分钟
Just give us five minutes.
谢谢
Please.
知道这是什么吗
You know what this is?
这是真的你
This is really you.
未来的你
Like, future you.
听我说  是这样...
Come on, look--
你告诉他们了吧
You told 'em, right?
我是准备告诉的  等这件事结束
I'm gonna tell them, yeah, when this is finished.
等这件事结束
When this is finished?
哪怕你要把他们领向一场外星人大战
Even though you're about to lead them through an alien war?
即使闪点事件之后
Even after Flashpoint?
你搞砸了所有事之后
After everything you've messed up?
你改变了所有人生之后
All the lives you've changed?
还是不准备告诉他们吗
You still don't think you should tell them?
告诉我们什么
Tell us what?
杰克斯和斯泰因教授收到来自未来巴里的信息
Jax and Professor Stein found a message from me in the future
说不能相信现在的我
saying that, right now, I can't be trusted.
为什么未来巴里要这么说
And why would future you say that?
也许是因为我回到过去改变了时间线
I think because I went back in time and changed the timeline,
现在这里的情况跟我离开前不同
and now things here are different than before I left,
包括你们其中一些人的生活
including some of your lives.
我们其中一些人  比如谁呢
Some of our lives? Like who?
西斯科
Cisco.
凯特琳  沃利
Caitlin. Wally.
狄格
Dig.
我
Me?
为什么  怎么了
Why? What happened?
显然你生了个女儿
Apparently, you had a daughter.
我生了个女儿  巴里
I had a daughter, Barry?
小约翰本来是小莎拉
Baby John was Baby Sara.
慢着  我理清一下
So, wait, you-- let me get this straight.
你是说
You just, uh--
你把我女儿从我的生活抹去
You just erased a daughter from my life?
是的
Yeah.
你不能回到过去  像这样
You can't go back and just change things
-改变事物  巴里  -我知道
- like that, Barry. - I know.
你知道我为了不改变历史事件多难受吗
You know how hard it is for me to not alter events?
我多想把我姐姐救活
To bring my sister back?
但我没这么做  因为我知道后果
But I don't, because I know the implications.
过去八个月  我们穿越时间
And all those aberrations we spent the last eight months
试着修复的那些偏差
traveling through time trying to correct--
你却决定你可以自己去创造
you just decided that it was okay for you to create your own?
我们应该早点告诉他们
We should've told 'em before.
各位  是莱拉
Guys? Guys, it's Lyla.
总统被支配者绑架了
The President's been abducted by the Dominators.
她现在需要我们
She needs us now.
好  你们去吧
Okay, you guys go.
好吗  这次我不参与
All right? I'm gonna sit this one out.
显然你们有超女  她跟我一样快
Obviously, you have Supergirl. She's just as fast as I am.
去救总统  我们晚点再谈这件事
Get the President. We can talk about this later.
你还相信我吧
You still trust me, right?
我一直都相信你
I'll always trust you,
但他们没这么容易被说服
but it might take more to convince them.
如果你需要我  我会赶过去
If you need me, I'll be there.
各位  这很疯...
Guys, this is cr--
这很疯狂
This is crazy!
大家一起去  包括巴里
Everyone is going, including Barry.
他不去我也不去
I-- I'm not going without him.
那你留下来  奥利弗
Then you'll be here, Oliver.
好吧
Okay.
知道吗  奥利弗  没关系
You know what? Oliver, it's okay.
我跟他们一起去
I will go with them.
我们去救总统
We'll get the President.
你跟巴里留下来
You stay here with Barry.
确定我们来对地方了吗
Sure we're in the right place?
这是总统的追踪器
Well, this is the last place
最后给出信号的地方
the President's tracer gave a signal.
肯定就在附近
Must be nearby.
没错  他在那里面
Yep. He's in there.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
我可以看见他
I can see him.
我有X光视线
Oh, I have X-ray vision.
你是可以通过那种小窥视镜
Oh. You can see everyone's bits
看透大家吗
with those little peepers, huh?
-不  我...  -不用管他
- No, I-- - Ignore him.
你为什么叫热浪
How did you get the name Heat Wave?
我的家人被我活活烧死
I burned my family alive,
我喜欢用火点燃事物
and I like to light things on fire.
真是多姿多彩的背景故事
Aah. Well, that's a colorful backstory.
我的精神病医生也是这么想
Well, my shrink thinks so.
顺便说下  我不会叫你超女
By the way, I'm not gonna call you Supergirl.
这样很蠢
It's stupid.
叫我卡拉吧
You could call me Kara.
也不能这么叫
That won't work either.
如果需要我帮助  你会喊什么
Well, what're you gonna shout if you need my help?
裙子
Skirt.
认真的吗
Seriously?
认真的
Seriously.
但我不会需要你帮助
But I'm not gonna need your help.
看  是总统
Look! The President!
救我出去
Get me out of here!
感觉不对劲
This doesn't feel right.
我也觉得  杰佛逊
I agree, Jefferson.
有东西在逼近
Something's coming.
把总统放了
Release the President!
我们知道你们会来
We knew you would come.
你们听到了吗  我可是听到了
Did you guys hear that? 'Cause I heard it in my head.
嗯  我们听到了
Yeah, we heard it.
如果大家都没被吓到
Well, if nobody else is freaked out by it,
那我也不惊慌
far be it for me to panic.
你无需伤害他
You don't need to harm him
来换取我们身上的东西
to get whatever it is you want from us.
放了他  你就不会有事
Release him and nothing will happen to you.
他不是我们的目标
He's not who we want.
这是个陷阱
It's a trap!
超女  做点什么
Supergirl, do something!
闪电侠在危机中消失
我没想过  奥利弗
I didn't think about it, Oliver.
我没想过未来
I didn't think about the future.
我太专注于过去
I was so focused on the past,
在今天之前我都没想过
I didn't think about it until now.
我改变了很多
I changed so much.
这是什么
What is this?
闪电侠在危机中消失
这是未来的报道
This is an article from the future.
这是关于我消失的报道
It's a story about me vanishing.
由朱莉·格里尔撰写
原本是爱瑞丝·韦斯特·艾伦写的
Used to be written by Iris West-Allen.
但现在  我不知道
But now, I don't know.
爱瑞丝有所改变了
Something's-- something's changed with Iris.
我们的未来有所改变了
Something's changed with our future.
天呐  我做了什么
God, what did I do?
巴里  这只是篇看起来奇怪的报章报道
Barry, this is a weird-looking newspaper article.
没有任何意义
It doesn't mean anything.
你别再把这件事怪在自己身上
You need to stop beating yourself up over this.
我很抱歉  但你怎能这么说
I'm sorry, but how can you say that?
整件事都是我的责任
I'm responsible for all of this.
也许是  也许不是
Maybe. Maybe not.
巴里  你做出了选择
Barry, you made a choice.
你想看见你父母再活过来
You wanted to see your parents alive again.
你真的知道
Do you honestly know anyone that,
换作是别人
if they were in your shoes,
不会跟你做一样的事吗
wouldn't do the same exact thing?
我也会这么做
I would do the exact same thing.
巴里  "金牌"号沉下去时
Barry, after the Gambit went down,
救生筏上有我和父亲还有个船员
it was me, my father, and a crewmember on a life raft.
在海上漂流
Lost at sea.
食物和水也许只够一人生存
Enough food and water for one person, maybe.
我爸拿枪射杀了那个船员
My father took a gun, shot the crewmember,
告诉我要活下去
told me to survive,
然后也射杀了自己
and then turned the gun on himself.
他朝自己的脑袋开枪
He shot himself in the head.
他牺牲自己  保我性命
He sacrificed himself so that I could live.
我无能为力  别无选择
Nothing I could do. No choice.
斯莱德·威尔逊在我和我妹妹面前
Slade Wilson drove a sword right through my mother's heart,
一剑刺入我母亲的心脏
in front of my sister and I.
我就在那里  我站在那里无能为力
I was there. I was helpless on the ground.
我无力去阻止  别无选择
I was powerless to stop it. No choice.
你以为我就不会想
Do you not think that I wouldn't give anything
穿越回去改变过去吗
to go back and to make things different?
你从来没告诉过我
You never told me that.
巴里  世界不会因为你
Barry, the world isn't different
改变时间线而有所不同
because you changed the timeline.
变化和悲剧都会发生
Change happens. Tragedy happens.
人们做出选择
People make choices,
那些选择影响其他人
and those choices affect everyone else.
你不是神  巴里
You're not a god, Barry.
各位  不管你们在哪里  我们需要你们
Hey, guys, wherever you are right now, we need you.
情况变得糟多了
Oh, things just got so much worse.
尖端科研实验室
各位
Guys.
我们能聊聊吗
Can we talk about this?
看来不能
Guess not.
他们怎么了
What's wrong with them?
我不知道  我们得搞明白
I don't know, but we need to find out.
好吧
Okay!
你这次真是搞砸了
You really did it this time!
真的吗
Seriously?
我说真的
Yeah, seriously.
-那是什么  -热视线
- What's that? - That would be heat vision.
好吧
Okay.
怎么回事
What is going on?
巴里和奥利弗留下来
Barry and Oliver stayed behind
其他人去救总统
while everyone went to go save the President,
但现在大家都疯了
but now everyone's crazy
于是上演了《杀死比尔》
and going all "Kill Bill" on the both of them.
支配者控制了他们的大脑
The Dominators have them under some sort of mind control.
他们不能永远被控制
They can't hold them off forever.
-我得赶过去  -你搞什么
- I got to get out there. - The hell you do.
仅凭他俩没法打败他们
They can't beat them by themselves,
尤其是超女现在是敌方
especially not with Supergirl against them.
沃利
Wally?
叫我闪电小子
Kid Flash.
沃利  快说话
Wally? Talk to me,
撑住
Hey! Come on.
各位  沃利伤得很重  但没死
Guys. Wally's hurt bad, but he's alive.
撤销大脑控制预计还要多久
Let's get an ETA on overriding the mind control!
-搞定  -胜利
- Bingo! - Yahtzee!
你先说  这是你的办公室
You go first. You go first. It's your office.
盐矿那里有奇怪的信号
There's a weird signal coming from the salt mines.
发现信号
我得说我本来打算那么说
For the record, that is what I was gonna say.
你能屏蔽吗
Can you jam it?
不能
Uh, no.
你还剩多少箭
How many of those do you have left?
应该不够用
Probably not enough.
这个走廊通往大楼的地堡
Okay, this hallway leads to a bunker under the building.
你尽量拖住他们
Just hold 'em off as long as you can.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
如果他们无法关上  也许她能
If they can't shut it down, maybe she can.
超女
Hey, Supergirl!
终于能比谁的速度快了
Let's finally see who's faster.
太慢了
Too slow.
-他在干什么  -他在惹怒她
- What is he doing? - He's making her angry.
但他知道超女是不可战胜的
But he knows Supergirl is invincible.
也许他在利用这点
Think maybe that's the point.
巴里
Barry?
各位  他们恢复了
Guys, they're back.
怎么回事
What happened?
你没杀死我  所以我还能活着
You didn't kill me, so my day's looking up.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你不是第一个被控制大脑的超级英雄
Hey, you're not the first superhero to be mind-controlled.
我知道你打算说什么
Okay, I know what you're gonna say,
但我必须这么做
but I had to do something.
很高兴你没事
I'm glad you're okay.
不要再那么做了
Don't ever do that again.
抱歉我一点也没觉得抱歉
Sorry. Not sorry.
来吧  跟我去检查一下
Come on. Let's get you checked out.
然后再聊那么做有多蠢
And then we can talk about how dumb that was.
好
Okay.
好什么
Okay what?
他们没发现你的潜力
They don't see your potential.
我发现了
I do.
我的其中一个天赋
One of my many gifts.
你要训练吗
You want to train?
我会训练你
I'll train you.
所以大脑被控制是怎样的
So, what was it like being all mind-controlled and stuff?
我不知道他有大脑能被控制
I didn't realize he had a mind to be controlled.
巴里  关于之前的事
Barry, about before.
不管有没有那条信息  我们都支持你
Message or no message, we're with you.
谢谢
Thank you.
超女呢
Where's Supergirl?
扫描整座城市确保
Scanning the city to make sure there aren't
控制你们的大魔怪都不在了
any more of the orbs that whammied all of you.
-现在怎么做  -我们打给莱拉
- Okay, so now what? - We call Lyla.
告诉她支配者来者不善
Tell her these Dominators aren't here peacefully.
莎拉
Sara!
大家都进去  快
Everybody inside! Go!